ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Hours and Earnings in the Leather Glove Industry, 1934 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Wages and Hours in the Leather Glove Industry, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- "Breezy" Wynn in Puerto Rico, 1957-1959 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Wynn Enterprises, Inc., 1957 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- "Breezy", 1955-1957 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Closings & Liquidations - Cotton Garment, 1970-1980 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Closings & Liquidations - Clothing, 1975-1983 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- "Breezy" Wynn, 1955 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- ACWA - The "Breezy Wynn" Case, 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- ACWA - The "Breezy Wynn" Case - Government Procurement Contracts, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- ACWA Military Procurement --- Surplus Manpower Committee - Report on Apparel Industry, 1952-1964 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- ACWA Organizations in Kentucky, 1963-1982 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- ACWA Organizations in Kansas, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- ACWA Organizations in Oregon, 1956-1960 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- ACWA Organizations in New Jersey, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- ACWA Organizations in California, 1955-1971 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- ACWA Organizations in Massachusetts, 1953-1979 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Record of Cleaning and Dyeing Minimum Wage Order #4 (NYS), 1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Record of Cleaning and Dyeing Minimum Wage Order #4 (NYS), 1939-1940 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Clothing Fund - Out of Business New Contributors Changes (Reports prepared for General Executive Board Meetings), 1970-1980 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Insurance Funds History, 1942-1964 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment - Out of Business New Contributors Changes (Reports prepared for General Executive Board Meetings), 1970-1980 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Press Clippings (April thru August), 1940 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Contract Inventory Listing Clothing Cotton Garment, 1942-1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Joint Boards, 1965-1975 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/84 - 6/30/84), 1984 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/84-12/31/84), 1984 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/85 - 6/30/85), 1985 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/85-12/31/85), 1985 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/86 - 6/30/86), 1986 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/86-12/31/86), 1986 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Murray H. Finley (President), 1983-1987 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Arthur Loevy (Executive Vice President), 1987-1989 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Charles Sallee (Secretary-Treasurer), 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Charles Sallee (Executive Vice President), 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Scott Hoyman (Executive Vice President), 1980-1989 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Jack Sheinkman(Secretary-Treasurer) (1/1/87-6/30/87), 1987 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/87-12/31/87), 1987 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/88 - 6/30/88), 1988 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/88-12/31/88), 1988 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/89 - 6/30/89), 1989 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/89-12/31/89), 1989 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/90 - 6/30/90), 1990 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/90-12/31/90), 1990 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/91 - 6/30/91), 1991 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/91-12/31/91), 1991 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/92 - 6/30/92), 1992 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/92-12/31/92), 1992 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (1/1/93 - 6/30/93), 1994 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Jack Sheinkman (President) - (7/1/93-12/31/93), 1993 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (June), 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (September), 1965 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (September), 1966 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (September), 1969 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations - Vol I, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations - Vol II, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Apparel Plant Information Survey Questionnaires, First Quarter - Vol I, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Apparel Plant Information Survey Working Materials - Vol II, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (September), 1972 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (Feb 72', June 74', June 75'), 1972-1975 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (September), 1975 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Cotton Garment Industry Documents (September), 1976 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Clothing Industry Documents (June), 1977 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Men's and Boy's Clothing Industry Documents (June), 1963 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Men's and Boy's Clothing Industry Documents (June), 1965 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations and Settlement, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations and Settlement, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Men's Clothing Negotiations - Background Material, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Men's Clothing Negotiations - Background Newspaper Clippings, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Chronology of Labor Negotiations and Collective Bargaining, 1939-1951 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Men's Clothing Negotiations, Background Material, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Men's and Boy's Clothing Industry Documents (June), 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Men's and Boy's Clothing Industry Documents (June), 1971 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Clothing Negotiations - Book 1 ACWA, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Clothing Negotiations - Book 2 ACWA, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Contract Analysis - Clothing Cotton, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Clothing Negotiations and Settlement, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Clothing Negotiations - Clobook Book 1, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Men's Clothing Negotiations - Book 1, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Men's Clothing Negotiations - Book 2, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Men's Clothing Negotiations - Volume I, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Men's Clothing Industry - Volume II, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Clothing Negotiations (Correspondence), 1985 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Clothing Negotiations - Book 2, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Clothing Industry Fact Book (CLOFAX) (February), 1988 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center - NY, 1950+ (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center - NY, 1960+ (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center of Chicago, 1954-1963 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Sidney Hillman Medical Center of the Male Apparel Industry of Philadelphia, 1951-1963 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center of Rochester, 1960-1965 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1973-1989 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation - Financial Statements, 1976-1979 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Health Centers, 1951-1964 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Health Center, 1952-1966 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Local 119 Health Fund/Reuben Block Health Fund, 1959-1971 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- ACWA - Medical Activities - Mental Health, 1964-1967 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Health Maintenance Organization (H.M.O.), 1974-1976 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- ACWA Health Centers & Health Services, 1973-1975 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- ACWA Health Centers & Health Services, 1975-1977 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Union Optical Plan, 1951-1956 (Box 99, Folder 15)
- ACWA Insurance - Miscellaneous, 1936-1950 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- ACWA Insurance, 1940-1944 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- ACWA Insurance, 1945-1947 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- ACWA Insurance, 1948-1949 (Box 99, Folder 19)
- ACWA Insurance, 1950-1953 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- ACWA Insurance, 1954-1957 (Box 99, Folder 21)
- ACWA Insurance, 1958-1959 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- ACWA Insurance, 1960-1969 (Box 99, Folder 23)
- ACWA Insurance, 1970-1979 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- ACWA Insurance, 1980-1989 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- ACWA Cotton Garment & Allied Industries Fund - Financial Statements, 1960-1974 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- ACWA Insurance Fund - Financial Statements, 1968-1972 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- ACWA Articles, 1950-1959 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- ACWA Articles, 1960+ (Box 100, Folder 6)
- ACWA Decade, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- ACTWU - Articles, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- ACTWU - Articles, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- ACTWU - Articles, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- ACWA - Articles - Merger with TWUA, 1970-1976 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- ACWA Publications + Leaflets, 1959-1975 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- ACWA Highlights in History, 1961-1962 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- ACWA Statements on Imports - Foreign Trade - Apparel, 1959-1975 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- Foreign Trade - Apparel - Impact of Imports on Industry and Employment, 1965-1972 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- Statement on Wages to National War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Men's Clothing Industry - Minimum Wage of 40 cents an hour, 1939-1941 (Box 100, Folder 17)
- ACWA Statement - Fair Labor Standards Act Amendments, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Southern Summer School (E. Tenn State U. Aug 26-31, Johnson City, Tn), 1979 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Deep South Administrative Staff July 26, Charlotte, NC., 1979 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Southern Regional Joint Board Spring Conference - Atlanta, GA. Fri & Sat, Apr 27-28, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Sunday, March 11, Conference of N. Carolina Locals at Local 1355, Fletcher, NC., 1979 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Hendersonville, NC. (3/10-11), 1979 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Southern Wage Conference March 24 and 25th, Greensboro, NC., 1979 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Southern Wage Drive, Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Southern Wage Drive, Clippings, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- MidWest - Chicago JT.BD. Officers &/or Delegates, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- MidWest - Chicago Joint Board - Tex.Div., 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Chicago Textile Industry Employee Benefit Fund, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Chicago Joint Board; Chicago Textile Industry Employee Benefit Plan & Midwest Textile Credit Union (Dunigan & Helms), 1981 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Chicago Textile Industry Health and Welfare Fund, 1971-1976 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Chicago Joint Board - Clothing Div., 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- MidWest - Chicago Joint Board. Laid Off Members/Officers Local 190T, 1983-1984 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Executive Board Meeting Sept. 5. 2:00-5:00 PM Holiday Inn - Chicago South, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- CHI Joint Board -- Chicago Textile Industry Employee Benefit Fund, 1981-1984 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- MidWest Region By-Laws, 1982-1984 (Box 101, Folder 18)
- MidWest Legal, 1981-1982 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- MidWest Region (Legal Matter) Local 1828 Sheila Nichols v. Wapakoneta Products Co and ACTWU Botkins, Ohio, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- MidWest - Organizing, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- MidWest Region Charter Application and By-Laws, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- MidWest - Organizing, 1976-1981 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- MidWest - Personnel, 1978-1985 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- MidWest Stevens' Port Huron, Mich. Plant for GM Carpets, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- MidWest Chicago Joint Board. General, 1982-1987 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- MidWest Region - Noel Beasley Director, August., 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 27)
- MidWest Region Marion Groce Director, 1980-1986 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- MidWest - General, 1981-1986 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- MidWest - Cincinnati Joint Board, 1980-1987 (Box 101, Folder 30)
- MidWest - Indiana-Kentucky Joint Board. General, 1982-1987 (Box 101, Folder 31)
- MidWest - Indiana-Kentucky Joint Board. Stephen McNew/Religion & Dues, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 32)
- Levi-Strauss Retirement Plan, 1969-1986 (Box 101, Folder 33)
- MidWest Kansas City Joint Board. General, 1976-1985 (Box 101, Folder 34)
- MidWest Ohio State Joint Board., 1977-1986 (Box 101, Folder 35)
- MidWest Local #224 Ohio State Joint Board., 1976-1985 (Box 101, Folder 36)
- Toledo Joint Board and Cleveland Joint Board Merger Discussions, 1976-1981 (Box 101, Folder 37)
- Dave Griffin at NY Office Tuesday, May 7, at 11 PM (Pres. CNCJB and Local 250), 1985 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Southern Local 253 Mount Vernon Mills, 1983-1986 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Southern Local 254 Columbia Pacific Mills Columbia, S.C, 1983-1985 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Local 324, Newberry, S.C. Deep South Region, 1976-1980 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Southern Local 689 Rome, Ga., 1970-1983 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Southern Local 710, 1982-1987 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Complaint Local 710 - T Joint Board Formation, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Southern Region - Local 281, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Mid West Local 281 Memphis, Tn Conna Krenik's Report, 1978-1981 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Southern Local 710, 1978-1981 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Southern Local 1093 Rock Hill, S.C., 1980-1987 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Southern Local 1355, 1985-1987 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Christmas Party Hendersville, SC East/West Rooms Holiday Inn, Dec 15th, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- Southern Local 1386 Clover, S.C., 1979-1984 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Complaint - Local 1355 (affiliation with Joint Board.), 1981 (Box 102, Folder 15)
- Southern Local 1355 Disaffiliation Problem, 1981-1985 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- Southern Local 1355 (By-Laws, 1977), 1977-1983 (Box 102, Folder 17)
- Southern Local 1465 Courtauld's Mobile, Ala., 1981-1982 (Box 102, Folder 18)
- Southern Local 1566, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 19)
- Southern Local 1604 Retirees' Club (5/82), 1982 (Box 102, Folder 20)
- Southern Local 1742 Knoxville, Tn., 1982 (Box 102, Folder 21)
- Local 1867 - Porritts & Spencer Wilson, N.C., 1980-1983 (Box 102, Folder 22)
- Southern Regional Joint Board- Viscount Hotel Atlanta, GA. Fri, Sat & Sun April 18-20, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 23)
- Southern Wage/Fringe Negotiations, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 24)
- Southern Wage Information, 1984-1985 (Box 102, Folder 25)
- Southern Textile Region Managers - Mon & Tues - Feb 10-11, Charlotte, NC, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 26)
- Southern Regional Textile Joint Board. Meeting and Conference Fri. Apr 26- Sun. Apr 28, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 27)
- Southern Textile Region Personnel Meeting, Atlanta, GA - Sun May 13, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 28)
- Southern Textile Region Staff Meeting, Americana Inn, Atlanta, GA. Wed-Thurs April 25-26, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 29)
- Trip to Atlanta, GA. With Murray Finley April 5-7, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 30)
- Greensboro Trip. Thurs, Oct 27, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 31)
- Southern Wage/Fringe Reopener, Negotiations, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 32)
- Deep South Regional Joint Board Capital Airport Inn, Atlanta GA. Fri-Sun, Feb 11-13, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 33)
- Mid South Regional Conference Charlotte, NC. March 20-21, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 34)
- Southern Wage Policy Conference. Charlotte, NC. Sun. March 12, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 35)
- Southern Tour with Murray Finley Oct. 6-11, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 36)
- Southern Wage Agitation Drives Effect on Southern Economy, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 37)
- Meeting of all Southern Locals -- Wage Re-Opening, Columbia, S.C. March 13, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 38)
- Southern Textile Wages, 1974-1978 (Box 102, Folder 39)
- Southern Wage Drive, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 40)
- Southern Wages, 1974-1978 (Box 102, Folder 41)
- Wage Agitation Drive (Economic Notes - North and South), 1978 (Box 102, Folder 42)
- Southern Textile Wages, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 43)
- Southern Wage Conference, Greensboro, N.C. June 15, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 44)
- Southern Wage Conference, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 45)
- Southern Wage Conference (Wage Policy Committee Meeting) Charlotte, NC. Sat. April 24, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 46)
- Deep South Regional Meeting, Atlanta. Friday, Dec 11, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 47)
- Sol Stetin (& Scott Hoyman) Atlanta, GA. Jan 30-31, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 48)
- Southern Wage Policy Committee, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 49)
- Wage Agitation - Southern Region, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 50)
- Deep South - Staff Meeting. Charlotte, N.C. November 7, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 51)
- Southern Regional Summer School. Watts Bar Dam. August 10-15, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 52)
- Deep South Staff Meeting, Charlotte. Friday Jan. 25, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 53)
- National Rally for Dignity and Justice. Laurel, Mississippi. May 17th., 1980 (Box 102, Folder 54)
- Southern Regional Conference Mid-South and Deep South. Spartenburg, SC. April 12., 1981 (Box 102, Folder 55)
- Southern Wage Drive, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 56)
- Southern Wage and OSHA Conference. Charlotte, N.C. March 8-9, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 57)
- Southern Wage Agitation Drive, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 58)
- Southern Wage Movement, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 59)
- Southern Wage Drive, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 60)
- The Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. (Committee #99-A), 1971 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Men's and Boys' Clothing, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Men's and Boys' Clothing, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Men's and Boys' Clothing, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Men's and Boys' Clothing, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Hosiery/Textile Mill, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Leather\Military Hats, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Leather, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Leather, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Leather, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Gloves, etc, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Gloves, etc, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Gloves, etc, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Hosiery, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Hosiery, 1971 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Hosiery, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 6)